http://www.whosyourva.com/privacy-policy

Contact UsUse the form on the right to contact us, or email me directly at info@WhosYourVa.com
*
Thank you!
LaCrosse WI/Seward Ak
USA
millane@whosyourva.com
Business/Real Estate Agent Support SpecialistSocial Media Management/Marketing Support Specialist
Home
Pricing
Benefits - Is a VA Right for You?
Able Millane Web Services
Why is it Smarter to Hire a VA?
Online Business Management
Meet Me
Photo Gallery
Why Choose Us?
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their "Personally Identifiable Information (PII)" is being used online.  PII, as used in US privacy law and information security is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context.  Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your PII in accordance with our website.What Personal Information do we collect from the people that visit, blog, website or app?When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address or other details to help you with your experience.When do we collect information?We collect information from you when you fill out a form or enter information on our site.How do we use your information?We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communications, surf the website or use certain other features in the following ways:To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service needs.How do we protect visitor information?We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.We use regular malware scanning.Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.  In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) Technology.We implement a variety of security measures when a user enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.  All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.Do we use 'cookies'?We do not use cookies for tracking purposes.You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies.  You do this through your browser settings.  Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.If you disable cookies, some features will be disabled that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.Third Party DisclosureWe do not sell, trade or otherwise transfer to outside parties your PII unless we provide you with advance notice.  This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operation our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.  We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety.However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third Party LinksWe do not include or offer third party products or services on our website.GoogleGoogle's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles.  They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users.  https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=enWe use Google Adsense Advertising on our website.Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.  Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the internet.  Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.We have implemented the following:Google Display Network Impression ReportingWe along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.Opting out:Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page.  Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out browser add-on.California Online Privacy Protection ActCalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy.  The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting PII from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with who it is being shared, and to comply with this policy.  See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbt51.dpuf.According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:Users can visit our site anonymously.Once this privacy policy is created we will add a link to it on our home page, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.Our privacy policy link includes the word "privacy" and can be easily found on the page specified above.Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes on our privacy policy page.Users are able to change their personal information by emailing us.How does our site handle do not track signals?We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising with a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place. Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking?No.COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the COPPA puts parents in control.  The FTC, the nation's consumer protection agency enforces the COPPA rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.  We do not specifically market to children under 13.Fair Information PracticesThe Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe.  Understanding FIPP and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.  In order to be in line with FIPP we will take the following responsive action should a data breach occur: We will notify users via email within seven days.We also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have the right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law.  This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights gains data users but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.CAN SPAM ActThe CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them and spells out tough penalties for violations.We collect your address in order to:Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.To be in accordance with CAN-SPAM we agree to the following:Not use false or misleading email subjects.Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance.Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests.Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails you can follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.  We will promptly remove you from all correspondence.Contacting Uswww.whosyourva.comWisconsin, 54665millane@whosyourva.com Edited 1/12/15
Endorsements
Privacy Policy
Created By: AbleMillane
